Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records concerning finances of the Graduate School, maintained by Dean Donald W. Taylor, 1969-1975; Accession 2004-A-151
  - Master of Arts in Teaching
    - 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - John Hay Fellows Program (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Science Program (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - History Program (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Training Secondary School Teachers (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Qualifications for Advanced Standing (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Advances and Temporary Loans (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Riot Provision - Education Legislation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Application Fee - Graduate School (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Assessment of Quality in Graduate Education, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Assistantship Data (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - B.A.-M.A. Degree Inquiries (General Correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - CentralClearance Use UniversityFacilities (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Class and Examination Schedules (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Coalition for a New University (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - College Fellows Affiliation (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - College Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Convocation - Incoming Students Material JPM (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cost of Education Allowance - Federal Fellowships and Traineeships, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Departmental Codes - IBM (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Discipline Report - President's Committee (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dissertation Readers - Outside (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dissertation Fee - Proration, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dissertation Information - Library (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dissertation Information - General (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Microfilming Dissertations (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - ETS Language Exam Scores - Departmental (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Requests for Evaluation of Students, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Faculty and Non-faculty Scholarship Plan (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fellowship and Traineeship Stipends, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Five-Year B.A. Experiment (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Foreign Language Requirements, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Foreign Language Testing Data (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - General Appropriation - Fellowships Request, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - General Appropriations Request - Graduate School Fellowships, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Grades - Graduate Students (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Grading, Quality Requirement, Extensions, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Graduate Affiliates
    - 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Yale Graduate Professional Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Graduate Record Examination Score Interpretation (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Graduate School Growth, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Graduate School House Committee File 2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Graduate Student Discipline Cases (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Graduate Student Full-Time Appointments to Faculty of Arts and Sciences (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Graduate Student Council (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Graduate Student Housing JPM - Questionnaire and Article (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Graduate Student Housing Rent Adjustments (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Graduate Student Teaching - Yale College and Graduate School (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Housing Committee - ERW, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Report, 1968 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Housing - Visiting Faculty (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Integration - HGS and HHH, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Intermediate Degree - JPM Article (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Junior Fellows (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Language - Requirements in the Sciences (Box 3, Folder 76 - 77)
  - Language Requirement (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Language Tests (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Language Tests - Foreign Students (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Master's Degree Language Requirements (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Language Requirements - Ph.D. Degree (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Language Reading Courses (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Language Substitution, 1963 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Committee on Language Teaching (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Loans - Miscellaneous Information (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Master's Degree Requirements- Entering Students, Fall 1967 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Terminal M.A. Programs to be Discussed with Graduate School Executive Committee, 1966 October (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - M.A.-LLB Joint Program Procedures, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - M.D.-Ph.D. Joint Program (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Master of Science Degree in Engineering - Part-Time Basis (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Negroes (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Numbering System of Courses (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Occupational Deferment - Graduate Students (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Proration of Dissertation Fee, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Proration of Tuition Due to Draft (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Readmission After Military Service (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Riots (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Revenues and Expenditures - Graduate School Exclusive of Fellowships (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Room Rental Charges, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Seminars - Governing of the University, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Sheffield Scientific School (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Statistics, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Statistics - Other Universities (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Student Affairs - Graduate School, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Student Activism (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Student Protests (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Student Record Keeping Procedures (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Summer Programs, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Student Suggestions (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Teaching Assistants - General (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Teaching Interns - Others Schools (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Committee on Teaching of Science (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Teaching Interns, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Terminal Date Extensions (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Transfer Requests (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Tuition Rates (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Tuition - Accounting Instructions, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - University College-JPM (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Work-Study Program - Summer (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Computer Science Program (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Concilium, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Records of the office of the dean, 1916-1969; Accession 2004-A-168
  - AAU - Graduate School Ratings (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admissions - Migration of Graduate Students (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions Policy (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Admissions - Increase (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agency Account - Dean's Fund, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Raid (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
  - School of Alcohol Studies (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Studies - Germany (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Army (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Army - Confidential (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Army - USSR Training (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Association of American Colleges - Directory of Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Communication Sciences Project (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Concilium on International Studies (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Communist Control Act (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conference Board Association Research Councils #2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Conference Board Association Research Councils - LAM (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Concilium on International Studies (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Concilium on International Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Concilium on International Relations, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Concilium on East Asian Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Council on Russian and East European Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Council on Southeast Asian Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Latin American Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committee on African Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee
    - F.A.S. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - FAS Survey, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Humanities (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Sciences (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - FAS - Social Sciences (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - FAS Lists (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Financial Analysis - University (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Fees (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Graduate Student Council (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Graduate Schools - Studies, etc. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Grading (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Grades - Analysis (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Heidelberg Affiliation (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - News Letter (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Association of Canada (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Alumni Associations (Other Schools) at Yale (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Alumni Board (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Alumni Fund - Graduate School (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - AGS Policy Committee (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Assistantships (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Association of Graduate Schools - AAU (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - AAU-AGS - General (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Board of Permanent Officers (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Council on International Studies, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Conference Board Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Dahl Report - Questionnaire Replies on Tenure (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Eastern Deans (Seven Dwarfs) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Faculty Research Grants, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Research Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Faculty Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Research Grants - Ford Stimson Funds, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 61 - 62)
  - Faculty Research Grants - Ford-Stimson Funds, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - General Correspondence - JPM (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - General Correspondence re: Students and Applicants for Admission (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Graduate Housing - Com. Building and Grounds (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Graduate School House Committee (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Joint Appointments Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Maintenance Budget (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Max Kade Fellowship Material, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - NASA Applications, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - NASA Predoctoral Training Grant Application, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - News Reports - Special (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Office of Provost, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Cuba Alumni Fellowship (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Dining Hall (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Dissertations - Microfilming (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Office of Educational Research (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Educational Testing Service #1 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Fair Employment Practices (Conn.) (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Fellowships - Federal and Fellowships - Taxation (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Fellowship Administrators Conference, 1962 November (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Committee on Financial Aid Administration (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Foreign Area Studies (Russia) - Canadian Foreign Officer Training (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Foreign Service Institute - State Department (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Foreign Students (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Fulbright (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - General Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Cooperative Research Projects HEW (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - IBM Training Program (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Italian Exchange Fellowships (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Language Requirements (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Law School (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Library Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Library - General (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Mutual Security Administration (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Nathan Hale Fellowship (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - National Defense Education Act (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 5, Folder 105 - 106)
  - National Policy Committee (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Peace Corps (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Ph.D. Degrees - Other Universities (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Ph.D. Training (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Postdoctoral Information (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - The Rand Corporation (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Research Fellows (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Rochdale Cooperative House (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Summer Housing (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Summer Registration, Health, etc. (Graduate Students) (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Teacher Training (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship (Box 5, Folder 119 - 121)
  - Woodward House (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Yale's Program of Arts and Sciences (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Yale Summer High School (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Loan Program - National Defense Student (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Marshall Scholarships (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Middle States Association Conference (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - New England Conference on Graduate Education (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - NIH and HSF Grants (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Selective Service (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - State Department (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Ventures (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Ventures, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - University Committee on Atypical Growth (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Council of Graduate Schools (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Education (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Educational Testing Service #2 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - General Correspondence -, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 139 - 141)
  - General Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - General Correspondence re: Grading Students and Applications for Admissions (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Graduate School Enrollment Statistics by Department (annual) (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Hickman Scholarship (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Summer Activities (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Alumni Fund Contributors - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Alumni Fund Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 148 - 149)
  - Fellowships and Loans, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 150 - 152)
  - Fellowships, Tuition, Loans, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 153 - 154)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships (Partial Lists, Info, etc.), 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Foreign Students (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Foreign Professors and Research Scholars (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - John Hay Fellows #2 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - House Education and Labor Committee (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Humanities Center for Liberal Education (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Inauguration, 1964 April (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Inquiries From Schools Regarding Graduate Students (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - International Affairs (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Inter-School Committee - Foreign Students (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - International Student Exchange (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Inter-University Cooperation (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Alumni Committee (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Army File, 1947-1949 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Army, 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Army (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Association of American Universities - Graduate Schools (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Ledgers, 1945-1955 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Association of Graduate Schools (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - Committee on Graduate Work (Box 8, Folder 180)
    - General (Box 8, Folder 181)
    - Committee on Testing (Box 8, Folder 182 - 183)
    - Committee on National Service and Graduate Education (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Connecticut Committee on Higher Education (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Conference Board Association of Research Councils - Fulbright and Smith-Mundt Act, 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - English-Speaking Union (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Fellowships (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Committee on Foreign Students (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Foreign University Survey (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Graduate and Professional Schools Committee (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Graduate Record Examination Survey (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - Housing of Women (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - International Relations (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Science Fellowships - FOA - OEEC (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Sundaram (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Teaching (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Yale Students for Returning Servicemen (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Dean's Fellowship Expenditures, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Dean's Scholarship and Fellowship Expenditures
    - 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 205)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 206)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 207)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 208)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 209)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Report of the Executive Committee on the Humanities, 1958 October 7 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Report of the Executive Committee of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1958 October 7 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Executive Committee FAS - Humanities (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - The Needs of the Departments of the Social Sciences During the Next Decade - A Report by the Executive Committee FAS to the University Council, 1959 March 2 (Box 10, Folder 214)
  - Social Science Report - Executive Committee FAS (Box 10, Folder 215 - 216)
  - Summary of Recommendation by the President's Special Committee, 1959 February 6 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - College Ratings
    - A-C, 1930- (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - D-H, 1930- (Box 10, Folder 219)
    - I-N, 1930- (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - O-R, 1930- (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - S-Z, 1930- (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Letter From Dean Furniss to R.M. Gorski, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Candidates for Degree, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Financial Background Studies Data (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Loans (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Financial Background Studies by Hartley Simpson, -1955 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Report on Consultations at Several Universities Concerning Policies Relating to Administration of Faculty (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Executive Committee FAS Survey of Universities, 1958 August 22 (Box 10, Folder 229 - 230)
  - Wesleyan University Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 231)
  - University of California (Box 11, Folder 232)
  - Faculty Information Forms (Box 11, Folder 233)
  - University of Chicago (Box 11, Folder 234)
  - Columbia (Box 11, Folder 235)
  - Survey - Harvard (Box 11, Folder 236)
  - University of Illinois (Box 11, Folder 237)
  - Princeton (Box 11, Folder 238)
  - Provost's Survey - Wesleyan (Box 11, Folder 239)
  - College Age Population (Box 11, Folder 241)
  - Connecticut Council on Higher Education Conference on the Future of Higher Education in Connecticut (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Inventory - First Floor (Box 11, Folder 243)
  - Inventory - Second Floor (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - Inventory - Third Floor (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Periodical Clippings - Higher Education (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - A.D. Ferguson - 114 HGS Ext 2089 (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Miscellaneous - Higher Education (Box 11, Folder 248)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Higher Education (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Registration Survey (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Graduate School Enrollment Study (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Higher Education in Connecticut Annual Enrollment Survey, Fall 1956 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Reports on Graduate Studies (Box 11, Folder 253)
  - America's Resources of Specialized Talent (Box 11, Folder 254)
  - Engineering (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Recommendations for Appointments
    - 139 - Physics Department (Box 11, Folder 256)
    - 141 - Physiology Department (Box 11, Folder 257)
    - 141A - Plant Science Department (Box 11, Folder 258)
    - 141B - Psychiatric Nursing Department (Box 11, Folder 259)
    - 142 - Psychology Department (Box 11, Folder 260)
    - 143 - Public Health Department (Box 11, Folder 261)
    - 143A - Race Relations Department (Box 11, Folder 262)
    - 144 - Religion Department (Box 11, Folder 263)
    - 145 - Romance Languages and Literatures Department (Box 11, Folder 264)
    - 147 - Sociology Department (Box 11, Folder 265)
    - 148 - Transportation Department (Box 11, Folder 266)
    - 149 - Zoology Department (Box 11, Folder 267)
    - 150 - Department of University Health (Box 11, Folder 268)
    - 151 - Institute of Far Eastern Languages (Box 11, Folder 269)
    - 152 - Library (Box 11, Folder 270)
    - 153 - Divinity School (Box 11, Folder 271)
    - 154 - School of Engineering (Box 11, Folder 272)
    - 154A - School of Fine Arts (Box 11, Folder 273)
    - 155 - School of Forestry (Box 11, Folder 274)
    - 156 - Law School (Box 11, Folder 275)
    - 157 - School of Medicine (Box 11, Folder 276)
    - 158 - School of Music (Box 11, Folder 277)
    - 159 - School of Nursing (Box 11, Folder 278)
    - 159A - Sheffield Scientific School (Box 11, Folder 279)
    - 160 - Yale Dames (Box 11, Folder 280)
    - 161 - Department of Public Affairs (Box 11, Folder 281)
    - 162 - Veterans (Box 11, Folder 282)
    - 163 - University Service Bureau (Box 11, Folder 283)
    - 164 - Legal Aid Association (Box 11, Folder 284)
    - 165 - Institute of Human Relations (Box 11, Folder 285)
    - 166 - Civil Engineering Department (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - 167 - Yale Housing Bureau (Box 11, Folder 287)
    - 168 - Association of Research Libraries (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - 169 - U.S. Civil Service Examiners (Box 11, Folder 289)
    - 170 - Student Appointment Bureau (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - 171 - University News Bureau (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - History of Medicine Committee (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Statistical Analysis: Financial Aid; Applicants - Admitted Only, Admitted w/ pay, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Admissions Statistics (Box 12, Folder 294)
  - Terminal Date List - For A.D.F. (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Departmental Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 296)
  - Departmental Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Tuition Income (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Award Recommendations, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 300)
  - 14 - Statistics (Box 12, Folder 301)
  - Graduate School Fellowship Budget, 1962 February 8 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Department Reports, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 303)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowships, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Department Ratings (No Zoology), 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 305)
  - National Education Association (Box 12, Folder 306)
  - General Policy and Regulations (Box 12, Folder 307)
  - National Science Foundation
    - Cooperative (Box 12, Folder 308)
    - Postdoctoral, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 309)
    - General Awards, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - Summer, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 311)
  - Admissions Data
    - 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 314)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 318)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 319)
  - Registration and Enrollment, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 320)
  - Committees, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 321)
  - House Committee (Box 12, Folder 322)
  - National Academy of Science (Box 12, Folder 323)
  - Yale College, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 324)
  - Fellowship Committee, 1961 March 21 (Box 12, Folder 325)
  - Graduate School Faculty Records, 1916-1932 (Box 13, Folder 326 - 328)
  - General Education Board Committee - Bishop Museum Committee (Box 13, Folder 329)
  - Graduate School Faculty Records
    - Division I, 1916-1932 (Box 13, Folder 330)
    - Division IV, 1920-1931 (Box 13, Folder 331)
  - President's Committee on Freshman Year (Box 13, Folder 332)
  - The Bingham Oceanographic Laboratory - Past, Present, and Future (Box 13, Folder 333)
  - The Bingham Oceanographic Laboratory - Past, Present, and Future (Box 13, Folder 334)
  - Registration Control (Box 13, Folder 335)
  - Fellowship Control (Box 14, Folder 336)
  - Fellowship Control, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 337)
  - Yale - Board of Permanent Officers (Box 14, Folder 338)
  - Dean Simpson's Committee (Box 14, Folder 339)
  - Non-Western International Studies (Box 14, Folder 340)
  - Facts and Figures - Non-West (Box 14, Folder 341)
  - Fellowships
    - Graduate School Fellowship Budget (Box 14, Folder 342 - 343)
    - Fellowships (Box 14, Folder 344)
    - Scholarship and Fellowship Award Lists (Box 14, Folder 345)
    - President's Fellowship Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 346)